(Han Hyo-joo)
(Park Hyung-sik)
(Jo Woo-jin)
(Lee Jun-hyeok, Park Joo-hee)
(Bek Hyun-jin, Moon Ye-won)
(Park Hyoung-soo, Jeong Woon-seon)
(Bae Hae-sun, Cha Soon-bae)
(Park Hee-von, Na Chul, Han Jun-woo)
(Kim Young-woong, Lee Ji-ha,
Lee Ju-seung, Song Ji-u)
(Hong Soon-chang, Lee Ju-sil,
Kang Han-saem)
=Happiness=
(This program includes
indirect advertisements.)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, places, corporations,
and events are fictional.)
=Episode 1=
(Seyang High's Pride and Joy
Jung Yi-hyun)
(Busted knee)
(Disgrace)
Get moving.
Give me that.
(Jung Yi-hyun!)
(I played Little League too,
so I know how you feel.)
(So come down. Let's talk here.)
Just talk from there.
-What is he saying?
-I don't know.
Then give him a megaphone too. Darn it.
Hey. I'll come up, so wait a minute.
(Independent study)
(Let's talk up there.)
Where's the staircase?
Why won't he come down?
(Seyang High School)
Focus.
Focus, and you won't hear
a bomb explode next to you.
Why aren't we leaving? Class is over,
and we can't concentrate anyway.
(Independent study)
Do you think Yi-hyun would like it
if all of you pour out right now?
(Independent study)
He's psychologically frail as is.
What if he jumps off impulsively
when he sees you?
I'm sure you'll be able to concentrate
very well at home then.
You'll let us go if he comes down, right?
Yes, I'll let you go immediately.
The police are talking to him now,
so don't aggravate me. Just take a nap.
You must be tired. You've been in school
longer than other kids.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Hey. I said not to aggravate me...
Fine. As long as you're quiet.
Everyone focus.
Focus on your books.
A bomb is about to fall.
Gosh.
Hey! I'll get you fully rehabilitated.
I give you my word.
If not, I'll make sure
you can become a cop.
So trust me and let's go down.
I don't want to be a cop.
Okay!
I'm a friend.
They said to go up and help talk to him.
Let's talk here.
I won't go there, so don't worry.
Calm down.
Sae-bom?
Hey, you!
Hey!
Hey, kid! What... Hey!
Who are you? Are you his girlfriend?
No.
Hey, we can't go home because of you.
Mister, I'll talk to him,
so wait right there.
What's wrong with the kids at this school?
(Seyang High School)
Is it too hard not playing baseball?
That's not it.
I came up for some air,
and suddenly cops
and ambulances showed up.
Who called them?
I'm watching to see how far they go.
I have nothing to do anyway.
There's nothing to do other than baseball?
Of course, not.
It was all I did my whole life.
I was pretty good too.
But look what happened to me.
How could I be okay?
I've done nothing my whole life,
and I was fine.
It's better if you did nothing.
I've been in a hospital for a while,
so I know.
It'll all become memories once they pass.
I can't play baseball ever again.
My life is over.
I don't know what to do...
What about you? What are you going to do?
Last week, it was a nurse.
Now, I'm thinking civil servant.
I need a steady income
so that I can move out,
but I keep changing my mind.
See? You're down too
about falling behind two years.
No, I'm not.
I'm saying our future is boundless.
It's okay, so just do it.
If you fail, so be it.
Gosh.
Like me.
What?
What happened?
Get him.
Hey, kid.
Hey.
Don't get me wrong.
It was intentional.
I pushed him onto the cushion.
Let's talk at the station.
-Wait.
-Hey.
Yi-hyun.
Tell him you don't want me to be punished.
He wants to arrest me.
Hey, Sae-bom.
Want to go out?
=Happiness=
(12 years later)
(Special Operation Unit)
SOU.
Get over here and treat him!
Where is he hurt?
Bullet wound to the chest.
He can't breathe.
He has a collapsed lung.
The bullet pierced the lung,
releasing the air inside...
Don't diagnose him, treat him!
(Trainee Lee Jong-tae)
Should I really do it?
Don't think. Just do as you learned.
Sir.
You'll break my ribs.
That's my clavicle, you punk.
Trainee Lee Jong-tae.
You just killed a team member.
TMP point deduction.
(Tactical Medical Practitioner training)
(TMP score)
Your acting was good.
-Was it?
-Yes.
Put your gloves on.
That way, he won't slip.
What are you doing?
-Will you really deduct points?
-Yes.
He was slow to make decisions and fearful.
If you're the standard,
everyone in this world would fail.
(Trainee Yoon Sae-bom)
-SWAT!
Here.
He has a bullet wound and can't breathe.
What must you do?
(Trainee Yoon Sae-bom)
So...
Wait!
Yoon Sae-bom!
What are you doing?
They started using this because of you.
Because you stabbed him in the chest.
And he ended up being transferred
to a patrol station.
I heard from him recently. He said
the patrol station was a perfect fit.
Really?
He even sent me a gift card.
What about me?
Why didn't he send me one?
He must have had his reasons.
I'm starving.
Let's go eat.
(Motel)
Front desk.
I hear it too.
The second floor?
Okay, I'll tell them.
What are they doing
in the middle of the day?
Sir.
If you break anything,
you'll have to pay for it.
Do you want to get beat up?
(The days are getting slightly warm,)
(but the fact that we can breathe
without wearing masks)
(makes it a happy day.)
(Although the world has changed
since before the Covid-19 pandemic,)
(we've learned to appreciate
average days.)
(I hope)
(you all have a happy afternoon)
(during which you can see
each other's faces and smiles)
(and look up at the blue sky
and take deep breaths.)
(Enjoy the rest of your day.)
(I'll be back tomorrow...)
(We never know
when there will be another epidemic.)
(Jung Yi-hyun)
Here.
Do you still want to play baseball
with your bum knee?
They pay me if you play as a ringer.
-What's the case?
-A murder.
You didn't even know that?
I came because I was told to.
I even gave up my day off
and a baseball game.
-You should be grateful.
-Ever so grateful.
-Here.
-Babe.
The next room reported it.
-When we came out...
-Excuse me.
-Who's the victim?
-The clerk.
Let's go.
-And then...
-What is going on here?
What did he do to his neck?
I don't know.
It looks like it was a blunt knife.
Maybe to make it hurt?
Who's the suspect?
The one staying in this room.
People complained like crazy
because he was so loud.
Who covered him up?
Did you cover him up?
No, sir. That was how we found him.
-Any witnesses?
-Not yet.
They found him like this.
Did they check the security videos?
The security...
Why you...
What about the security videos?
They're checking them now,
but they don't have any footage
of the suspect leaving.
He covered the dead
before fleeing the scene.
But he wasn't caught leaving on camera.
He must've filled out an entry form.
But we won't get access, I'm sure.
Since it's a violation of privacy laws.
Murderers don't have rights.
We should round them all up
and send them to prison.
I just don't get it.
Not you.
What?
I assume they didn't look in here.
(Jung Yi-hyun)
Hey, I know you're the type to drill
into the investigation with pure luck--
I'm not.
Someone I know is way more...
Sir.
Come out.
Are you joking around?
You're dead meat if you are.
Darn it.
I looked him in the eyes.
Hey, we caught the criminal.
So don't come in.
Come in later.
(Resident ID Card, Sung Woo-je)
Did you do it, Mr. Sung Woo-je?
I don't know.
Did you cover the body
because you were scared to look at it?
But why did you kill him?
You can't remember that either?
I think I had a dream.
Was that dream about killing him?
Covered in blood like this,
you weren't able to run away anywhere.
And the police barged in
when you weren't in your right mind.
So that's probably why you hid.
But where's the weapon?
How did you kill him in your dream?
You're right.
The court won't accept it
if we don't have the weapon.
Well...
I was strangely thirsty.
Did you bite him?
(Special Operation Unit)
Give me one more.
(One main side dish per person)
Are you a farmhand?
Why do you eat so much?
I'm upset, so don't say anything.
Here.
If you have something to say, go ahead.
(Seyang Forest Le Ciel:
Special supply of public rental sales)
What are you looking at?
You know where
the National Police Agency used to be?
It's currently under development.
They're building apartments there, right?
It's been decided three police officials
will receive the special supply.
Really? What are the conditions?
My wife's dream is to move
into that new apartment.
Seniority, number of dependents,
and marital status are all scored,
but arrest records and performance scores
take up the highest proportion.
The apartment is yours if you get picked.
It's hitting the jackpot.
Who do you think we can arrest?
A terrorist?
You never know what'll happen.
If I show them something today...
What're you going to show them?
I'm thinking about it.
Go easy on the baseball.
Be careful not to get hurt again.
Got it.
(I'm His Savior)
Do you have a religion now?
It's a friend.
I'm his savior.
What's up?
Your unit name popped up
during the investigation.
(How come?)
You're in charge of trainees
these days, right?
The culprit bought some drug
from an SOU trainee.
I heard it's a completely legal drug.
That just means you'll never get caught.
Do you have any drugs left?
I received about 3 or 4 pills,
but I think I took them all.
(What's the trainee's name?)
Lee Jong-tae.
Lee Jong-tae?
SOU!
(Trainee Lee Jong-tae)
(Anyway, I'm letting you know
we're sending you paperwork.)
Good job.
If I find out the organization,
that's going to boost my arrest records.
What do you mean?
I'm just letting you know.
Gosh.
I'm going to be right back,
so guard my food.
It's more important than food?
(Follow the code of conduct
to prevent re-spreading!)
That's so not like her.
Don't worry. I warned everyone
not to eat your pork cutlet.
What are they doing?
Don't tell me they're having sex here.
Those punks.
Trainee Lee Jong-tae?
Trainee Lee Jong-tae!
Save me!
What's wrong with him?
Stop right there, Lee Jong-tae.
Seung-young, take him outside!
It's your pelvis next.
What is that?
How would I know?
I'll stay here, so go get him some help.
Come on.
Emergency! Is there no one here?
This is a real situation!
Ma'am.
Please call me an ambulance.
Ma'am...
Get me the shelf.
Be careful not to get bitten.
(I'm His Savior)
(Let's save hot water!)
(-What is it?)
-You should've told me he's dangerous!
I almost died
I almost died!
What do you mean? Why would you die?
How is he fine after being shot?
Who shot who? Are you okay?
Of course, I'm fine.
How did you catch someone like that
without a gun?
I persuaded him.
Was that even possible?
Were you able to communicate with him?
Tell me in detail what happened.
Did you meet Lee Jong-tae?
(I did.)
Did he try to bite you?
You know very well.
What kind of ridiculous--
(Hello?)
(Hey, Yoon Sae-bom.)
(Are you okay?)
(Answer me! Hey!)
I am.
Hey, why didn't you answer?
You scared me for a second.
Senior Officer Yoon.
This is the ladies' room.
The man you shot.
There's a chance
he has an infectious disease.
What kind of infectious disease?
We're looking into that now.
(Sae-bom, who are you talking to?)
(I'm His Savior)
This is Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok
of the Central Disaster Countermeasure
HQ's Crisis Management Center.
Senior Officer Yoon will call you back.
Hand me your weapon
and cooperate with the investigation.
Who are you people?
(Warning)
You can have my pork cutlet.
Sae-bom.
The National Police Agency
will issue instructions shortly.
Officially,
what happened earlier was an accident.
Remember to keep it confidential.
We're taking her
as she might have contracted the disease.
(I'm His Savior)
(Special Operation Unit Is Dedicated
to Keeping Our Nation Safe)
-Yes.
(-Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok?)
(No, don't hang up.)
I'm Senior Officer Jung Yi-hyun
from Seyang Police Station.
Could you please briefly tell me
what's going on?
Senior Officer Yoon
needs to be tested as she had contact
with an infected trainee.
But she's okay now, right?
She's already been vaccinated
since she's an essential worker.
What kind of infection
are you talking about?
We'll look into it and find out.
-I have to go.
(-It was Lee Jong-tae, right?)
(The infected trainee.)
We've actually arrested a murder suspect
who was in contact with him.
Did you say "murder"?
(He bit a man's neck.)
Is that related to the infection?
Seyang Police Station, right?
I'll meet you there.
(Just a moment.)
Should everyone who had contact
with infected individuals be quarantined?
If they were bitten or scratched.
(Special Operation Unit Is Dedicated
to Keeping Our Nation Safe)
(Seyang Police Station)
If they weren't bitten or scratched,
it's fine.
You are Han Tae-seok, right?
Where is Sae-bom?
She's being tested somewhere safe.
(Jeil Auto Service)
(The 3rd Wonjung University
Anti-Redevelopment Protest)
(Wonjung University
School of Engineering)
(Stop)
(Central Disaster Countermeasures
Headquarters)
(Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok)
You're a soldier,
but you work in the civil sector.
We must work together in times of crisis.
So you're saying
this disease makes people bite others
once they're infected?
We believe that it's a viral variant
that affects the brain.
When bitten, you either die of blood loss
or get infected.
Goodness.
Now, they bite to infect
as if airborne transmission wasn't enough?
The infection routes are very limited,
so don't worry.
Please get back to your duties.
Wait, hold on.
We don't have to be quarantined, do we?
Just be sure to sign
the declaration of secrecy.
The suspect said
he took some kind of pill.
He said he got it from the trainee.
Do you
have that pill?
No. Maybe it's not an infectious disease.
Don't you think
it's a side effect of a hallucinogen?
That is unlikely,
but it could have had an effect.
Please call me
if you manage to find the pills.
(Meeting Room)
Senior Officer Jung Yi-hyun.
Are you playing baseball again?
I had high hopes for you
back in high school.
The thing is,
I can't run fast anymore.
That's too bad.
He must be a huge baseball fan.
He recognized you.
Hey. You requested a drug test, right?
Yes. I've handed over his hair sample.
I'll text you a phone number.
Ping the location for me.
Hey, where are you going?
To find the pills.
(Police Line, Under Investigation)
Jung-guk.
I found it.
(I'm calling you so you won't waste time.)
I just got the results back.
He's clean.
Seriously?
Yes. I suppose
he has the infectious disease after all.
I wonder if it's okay
for me to go home tonight.
If I bare my teeth in front of my wife,
-But...
(-she'll knock them all out.)
Then what about the pill I found?
It could be a cold remedy, painkiller,
or multivitamin.
Who knows? It could be anything.
(Stop wasting your time.
Just go home and get some sleep.)
(Super Rookie Baseball Academy)
Hey, Il-ho.
Hey! Why didn't you play today?
Come with me.
Hey, either call me
or at least pick up when I call.
What was I supposed to do?
Okay, I heard you.
Anyway,
take a look.
What's that?
Some kind of drug.
But I don't know what it is.
Why are you giving me a drug?
Don't get the wrong idea.
Hear me out first, okay?
You got kicked out for using drugs.
I thought it was an herbal tonic...
Seriously. And you call yourself a friend.
That's not true.
You did it to play baseball better.
I wanted to play well too,
but it didn't work out.
Don't bring that up. It's all in the past.
Yes, in the past.
You got your act together
and studied hard afterward.
Sports physiology and computer science.
This is important, that's why.
This isn't a drug.
Why not?
See that serial number?
Who puts in that much effort for a drug?
They don't brand the stuff.
This was made by a pharmaceutical company.
Check the pharmaceuticals database.
-Look it up for me.
-Me? When do you need it by?
Right now.
Wake me when you find it.
Open wide.
Are you drawing blood too?
What is this place?
It's not a hospital.
It looks like a school.
We can't let an infected man
who may bite people's necks
loose in a crowded place.
Will I end up like Lee Jong-tae?
Just kidding.
I won't bite you.
-You'll get hurt.
-Exactly.
Give me some answers.
I thought you were putting ointment on it.
What should I do until we get the results?
Give your statement.
Tell me what happened today.
I saw Lee Jong-tae
attacking a fellow trainee,
so I tried to stop him.
How did Lee Jong-tae appear?
He looked very bad.
A little more specifically.
Both of his eyes looked white and cloudy
like he had cataracts in both eyes.
He tried to maul me
as if he were an animal.
I shot him twice,
but he didn't seem to feel pain.
Is this
something like rabies?
It's similar.
My detective friend said
he was probably high.
If someone goes insane
and mauls another person,
the police will believe
it is drug-induced.
Because that is the easiest answer.
And it's easier for you
if it's an infectious disease.
People see what they believe.
However,
aren't you a cop too?
Well... We specialize
in terrorist attacks.
The police agency pays our salaries,
that's all.
Is Lee Jong-tae
all right?
He's recovering miraculously.
I'll find you a place to rest
while we wait for the test results.
Wait. May I get my phone back?
I'll bring a phone to your room.
(Unknown Caller)
Hello?
(Look at this mess you got me in.)
Sae-bom? Are you okay?
Yes. It's cleaner than
the civil servant apartment.
(You know that place is
over 50 years old.)
(The roof leaks when it rains
and it's freezing in the winter.)
How could they squeeze three people
into one unit?
I'm so cold.
Do they not care about
the electricity bill?
How do you feel? Did you get tested?
(Yes. Everything but a colonoscopy.)
I got a complete physical otherwise.
They say to stay here
until the results are out.
I explained to your mom.
You couldn't wait half a day?
Hey, no news is good news.
(Don't worry.)
(I told her she won't be able
to reach you because of training.)
True. You're not that clueless.
I'm looking into this too.
Anyway, where are you?
No clue. It looks like a college dorm.
I'm sure they won't kill me.
(I don't feel sick.)
(I'll just chill until I get the results.)
We got the drug test results
for our suspect.
He's clean.
Really?
Is it really an infectious disease?
I think it was drugs.
You really are a cop.
What do you mean?
Just something.
Anyway, I'll catch the perp
so that you can sleep at night.
Just rest there for a bit. Okay?
Okay. I'll be waiting.
It's late. Good night.
(Lytta Virus)
(Name: Yoon Sae-bom)
(Virus not detected.)
(Potentially the first antibody.
Must monitor closely.)
(Personnel Records,
Name: Yoon Sae-bom)
(Graduated high school 2 years late
due to car accident during grade school.)
(Extremely calm in any situation. Smart.
Extraordinary instincts. Too curious.)
(Super Rookie Baseball Academy)
Hey. Wake up. I found it.
What?
You found it? Let me see.
Next.
Next?
What's that?
An experimental pneumonia medicine.
You know how everyone researched
antivirals during Covid.
What was when it came out,
but it was pulled
because of its side effects.
Side effects?
Addiction, hallucination,
fluctuation of emotions...
It enhances concentration too.
It has a perk too.
Why didn't the drug test pick it up?
Not everything that makes you loopy
is an illegal drug.
It has to be named an illegal drug.
Il-ho.
What if...
What if this makes people rabid
or something like that?
It would be mayhem.
This sold pretty far and wide.
But that wouldn't happen.
Why not?
There haven't been any problems so far.
Why would there be one now?
(Warm and reliable Seyang Police
with the residents)
Did you locate the phone?
Hold on.
It was some kind of college.
Is it a student?
(Wonjung University)
Isn't this a college only in name?
That person must've been a terrible student.
That person must've been
a terrible student.
-Thanks.
-Hey.
Was I too harsh?
There's no one to wake me up,
and I don't have to go to work. How nice.
It's cold.
Ms. Yoon Sae-bom. Come outside.
Lieutenant, when did you...
Are the test results out?
We're going to test you again.
Lieutenant.
Tell me before you remove
a piece of my skin today.
Or I'm really going to feel hurt.
Are there other patients here?
Lee Jong-tae?
Let me talk to him for a second.
You can't.
Ms. Yoon!
It won't take long.
Are you okay?
It's a bit cold,
but I'm fine.
Do you remember getting shot by me?
Yes.
What about biting the other trainee
and attacking me?
I'm not sure.
So you do.
Ms. Yoon, back away.
He might be dangerous.
It's all right.
He looks fine.
Did you go crazy after taking some drugs?
Where did you get them?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The guy you gave the drugs to
has already been arrested.
You know you'll be additionally punished
because you're a police officer, right?
See this?
You did this to me, Jong-tae.
They say it's an infectious disease here,
but I'm not entirely sure.
I need to know
whether this is a disease
or if it's because of the drug,
Jong-tae.
That way, I can get tested at ease.
Can't I drink some water?
He absolutely can't!
I'm so thirsty.
She says you can't.
I'm thirsty.
Hey, what are you doing?
Open your eyes. We're talking.
Hey.
Lee Jong-tae.
Give it your best today.
Come on!
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok,
you're there, aren't you?
(No development plans for
Wonjung University's specialized street.)
(Residents, do not be deceived.)
(You're approaching your destination.)
(Opposing redevelopment and reconstruction
without alternatives)
(You've arrived at your destination.)
(Stop)
(Route guide will end.)
What brings you here?
Isn't this Wonjung University?
It was shut down due to insufficiency.
The military is currently using it.
(Jung Yi-hyun)
I'm with the police.
May I meet the person in charge?
(Jung Yi-hyun)
I'm afraid you can't.
This is a military classified area.
Then,
pass along a message
to Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok
that I brought the drug
I mentioned before.
Let him in.
You made me meet Lee Jong-tae on purpose,
didn't you?
You even installed surveillance cameras.
I wanted to know when he'd feel thirsty.
Thirsty?
When infected,
people lose reason and bite others.
They feel severe thirst,
but water can't quench it.
Even if they return to normal,
they keep feeling thirsty
and lose reason again.
We're looking into the conditions
when they feel thirsty.
I was curious
what Lee Jong-tae would be like
once he saw you.
So you wanted to know what he'd be like
once he saw the person who shot him?
He recognizes his family,
but I was wondering about others.
That wasn't the only thing.
His heart was beating slowly,
he seemed to feel less pain,
and his wounds healed quickly.
It'll make a lot of money
if it can be controlled.
Is that why
you're investigating it in secret?
Though it's not highly contagious,
it will scare people.
The degree of fatigue concerning
infectious diseases is already high.
There's no reason to make a fuss.
But why do you have
the air conditioner on?
The outbreak of the disease slows down
under low temperatures.
Is this also a test?
To see if I'm thirsty or not.
The test result showed
you're totally fine.
But I'm not such a lucky person.
Get some rest for the time being.
You mean, here?
No. Wherever you'd like.
Are you sure? Is that allowed?
It can be done if we say
you were hurt physically and mentally
while serving our country.
And we'll have to draw your blood
every two weeks.
You're not exhibiting any symptoms yet,
so you may already have antibodies.
(Temporary Pass)
(Important)
I guess I'm kind of important.
Do me one more favor.
You said earlier
that I served my country well.
Then I want the highest score
on my performance review for this year.
Sorry?
The public rental apartment in Seyang.
They reserve a few units for the police.
But it's a point system.
Marital status, number of dependents,
seniority, and performance review scores.
They add it all up.
I suppose you have that much influence.
Am I wrong?
I think I could arrange that.
You've been managing
a pretty good record anyway.
I'm the best.
I was born to prevent
and fight terrorist attacks.
I'm glad we're on the same page.
We don't shake hands anymore.
No, my phone.
Do you not serve breakfast here?
That's so petty.
Thank you. I'll go home and savor this.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't dislike you,
but the age gap is too big.
The highest performance evaluation score
won't be enough.
You'll need more points.
Do you have plans to get married soon?
Plans? I'll start planning now.
Are you not worried?
I'll get one of the apartment units,
no matter what.
So you don't need to worry about that.
I'm talking about what you saw
yesterday and today.
If things go wrong,
the world we knew up until yesterday
could collapse.
Will something change if I worry?
The world might not collapse after all.
Ma'am.
Where are my clothes?
We burned them.
I see.
Then do I have to go home like this?
Sae-bom! Hey.
Are you all right? Let me see.
You still don't trust me.
My feelings are actually hurt.
I'm fine. I can go home.
I'm sorry for getting you into this.
Your face looks gaunt.
Really?
It's because I didn't have any breakfast.
By the way, how did you get in here?
Did they bring you in?
Were you bitten too?
No, I came to save you.
Wait here.
I have to go talk to someone quickly.
Impressive.
Looks like you could play baseball again.
Is this
that pill?
That's right.
Apparently, it's a failed pneumonia cure.
Tons of people have taken it,
so it couldn't have caused the madness.
But I promised I'd find it,
so there you go.
Just because it was fine yesterday,
it doesn't mean it'll still be fine today.
I'll be off, then.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Yes. He was right next to me all along.
Yi-hyun.
Are you seeing anyone by any chance?
What? That's so random.
-Are you?
-No.
Do you snore
or grind your teeth in your sleep?
I don't think so.
Then how about we get married?
Yi-hyun. Tell him you don't want me
to be punished.
He wants to arrest me.
Hey, Sae-bom.
Want to go out?
No.
Hey, I told you that day
that I was only joking.
I'm not joking.
I mean it.
=Happiness=
(If people suddenly start going crazy...)
(Missed Call: Wife)
You asked me to gather intel
on Han Tae-seok.
(I really can't stand that guy.)
I own a home now.
(It's locked. The units on this floor
and below are public rental units,)
(The ones on the upper floors
are for general sales.)
(We welcome all new residents.)
(The ones on the upper floors
are for general sales.)
(A reporter called me.)
There is a way
(-to make money and stay safe.)
-Lee Seung-young!
(There's a problem at the dormitory.)
Where are the critically-ill patients?
(But they're alive.)
(If we stall, more people will be hurt.)