(Han Hyo-joo)
(Park Hyung-sik)
(Jo Woo-jin)
(Lee Jun-hyeok, Park Joo-hee)
(Bek Hyun-jin, Moon Ye-won)
(Park Hyoung-soo, Jeong Woon-seon)
(Bae Hae-sun, Cha Soon-bae)
(Park Hee-von, Na Chul, Han Jun-woo)
(Kim Young-woong, Lee Ji-ha,
Lee Ju-seung, Song Ji-u)
(Hong Soon-chang, Lee Ju-sil,
Kang Han-saem)
=Happiness=
(This program includes
indirect advertisements.)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, places, corporations,
and events are fictional.)
-What's going on?
-Why are soldiers here?
What happened?
-What's going on?
-Tell us.
Why won't you say anything?
(When making an infectious disease
spread rampantly among my people,)
(if people who call upon me
leave their evil ways)
(and pray to me and seek my countenance,)
(I will hear from above)
(and I shall forgive them
of their sins and heal them.)
(I shall set my eyes and ears)
(on what happens here.)
(The believers have been set apart
and made holy,)
(and...)
One of the homeless had pneumonia,
so they gave him medicine.
It was donated,
so they weren't aware of its side effects.
(Stay for a warm meal.)
=Happiness=
(There are reports coming in
from all around the world)
=Episode 2=
(There are reports coming in
from all around the world)
=Episode 2=
(about a disease that makes people bite
people's necks and drink their blood.)
(Health officials stated
that they have not been verified.)
(However, similar incidents
are occurring domestically as well.)
(At one homeless shelter Seyang,)
(over ten homeless people)
(who were at the shelter died.)
(Authorities have stated
that a fight had broken out)
(which resulted in the deaths.)
(They are concerned...)
(Deadly Fight at Seyang Homeless Shelter)
Rabbit food again?
Sae-bom. Are you okay?
Yes. I got tested and recharged.
What's going on?
Did you know
that they stopped the training?
They shut down the training room
where Lee Jong-tae had his outbreak.
Look. This is that guy, isn't it?
(Deaths not caused by fighting,
another infectious disease suspected)
Yes. Wow, he's pretty powerful.
Maybe something big is happening.
If people suddenly go crazy like that...
There is a cure, right?
I don't know.
I think they're trying.
I got a call from a reporter.
He said he'd pay me if I told him
what happened here.
Me too.
Darn it. He must've contacted everyone
on our team.
Hey. Don't respond.
We signed a confidentiality agreement,
remember?
Right.
Are you back?
No. I got a paid leave for six months.
I packed my things and sent them over
and stopped by to say bye.
You're moving out of the dorm?
You worked so hard to decorate it.
It's okay.
I got a new place.
An apartment.
-You got a loan?
-No.
Remember that apartment complex
I told you about?
The one set aside for the police.
I remember. It's based on
your performance evaluation.
I got the highest score,
but I was still short on points.
So I'm getting newlywed points.
Wait. So... You're getting married
for the points?
Yes.
With whom?
This guy who asked me out
when I was young.
I had turned him down back then,
but I asked just in case
he was still interested.
It's not because I have
no respect for you.
It's because
it has always been a dream
to have my own place.
Gosh.
For the clothes that were incinerated.
Thank you.
I feel like we've gotten closer.
She's so cold. Very cold.
Are you short on points?
Yes, but...
I only suggested it
because I'm interested in you.
You're decent looking
and can provide for yourself.
Hey. I'm a better catch than you think.
Being two years older is nothing.
And it's a new construction.
You'll regret missing out.
Hey. You won't find a friend like me
anywhere else.
Fine.
I'm asking you
to marry me.
I know.
I said okay.
He said okay.
I see. Okay.
Sure.
So... Congratulations on your wedding.
Thanks.
-When do you move in?
-Today.
This?
It's from when Lee Jong-tae scratched me.
It won't heal.
Did it get infected?
No. They want a blood sample
every two weeks.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What?
Yes, I'm fine.
(I'm His Savior)
Are you going to take that?
Yes.
Be right back.
(Special Operation Unit
dedicated to the security of our country)
I'm heading home now.
I'll unpack once the movers get there,
so take your time.
-Okay.
-Bye.
You are so devoted.
(Follow the code of conduct
to prevent re-spreading!)
(Special Operation Unit
dedicated to the security of our country)
(Seyoung Special Operation Unit)
So? Did you give it some thought?
How much will you give me?
Well... I spoke with my chief director.
If you have a video
and we get exclusivity,
we can give you a good amount.
Get in.
Let's talk comfortably.
It's okay.
Seung-young. What are you doing?
Here.
(Seyang Police Station)
Thanks.
How did you remember a photo
from 12 years ago?
I almost died that day.
Anyway, congratulations.
You pulled it off.
This was unexpected though.
-Step aside.
-Why? What is it?
It's a gift.
My wife started a new business.
Don't worry. She's fine now.
She's healthy.
We can do takeout and delivery.
Give it out in your building.
It'll only be hard for your wife.
You should make some...
Also,
remember how you asked me
to dig into Han Tae-seok?
I'll spread the word.
What did you find out?
He's an infectious disease specialist.
There's a program that sends
military academy students
for training at med school.
He got a medical license and was
a medical officer until he was discharged.
Then he worked
at a pharmaceutical company.
He was a manager for
increasing competitiveness
or something like that. And look...
(Han Tae-seok
sued for assaulting Chairman Choi Seok-ju)
From when he was in trial for assaulting
the chairman of a pharma company.
(Han Tae-seok
sued for assaulting Chairman Choi Seok-ju)
He didn't look like the type.
The calm ones are scarier
when they snap.
Anyway, he was found not guilty
and then he returned to the military.
To Central Disaster Countermeasures.
That's odd.
Stay away from him as much as possible.
You may get hit by a stray bullet.
Got it.
-Bye.
-Hey.
Let me know if you run out of rice cakes.
-Okay.
-Later.
I want to stay away from him too,
but I have a feeling I won't be able to.
(Le Ciel, Welcome new residents)
Well...
I keep thinking about that trainee
that I had administered first aid to.
Why?
He isn't doing well.
The same as Lee Jong-tae.
Even his family can't visit.
I asked guys who were dispatched to CDCH,
and they said
once you go in,
you don't come out alive.
I did.
Yes.
Only you.
You were the only one.
Will they be okay?
What if they all die in there?
Finding happiness
is hard.
You scared me.
Sorry. You should be careful.
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
That startled me.
Fifth floor please. Thank you.
Please wear a mask when you're indoors.
Okay. Sorry.
That jacket.
Where did you get that?
It looks authentic.
I'm in Special Ops.
Really?
You're really in Special Ops?
You're an anti-terrorism tactical agent?
Yes.
Can you get me a t-shirt
from Special Ops?
One with "SOU" on the front
and "Special Operation Unit" on the back.
In large.
I'll look into it. You wanted a large?
Yes, please. I'd really appreciate it.
I'm on the 15th floor.
What a character.
You're home early.
We moved.
We have to eat jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk.
I expected as much
and looked up restaurants nearby.
There was a photo from that day?
Jung-guk had the file.
Wow.
So I had it blown up.
Don't you like it?
Well...
But...
This wasn't that great a memory for you.
Do you like it?
Hey!
Stand straight.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Look at this whenever life gets tough
and hang on.
Okay.
You said the district office may come
to inspect us
to see if we're really married.
This should suffice
to explain why we got married.
It is a very strong motive.
Right. It looks like
we have quite a story.
I like the handcuffs.
When else would I be handcuffed?
Are you giving out rice cakes?
It's Jung-guk's side business.
He asked me to spread the word.
-I'll give them out...
-No.
I'll do it.
You should unpack
and order jjajangmyeon.
I want an extra-large serving.
Okay.
Be careful.
(Who is it?)
I moved in across the hall.
Are your parents home?
Hi.
Thank you.
Bye.
It won't open.
The floors below this are public housing.
The floors above are regular.
They blocked the doors
so people from below couldn't go up.
How do you know all that?
I know everything.
The other kids at school call
public housing kids poor.
How do people come down from above?
There's an elevator.
I see.
Are you going downstairs?
Yes.
One house is empty
and a lady lives alone in the other,
but she didn't come home yesterday.
You know everything, don't you?
That's better.
Come on.
Is it okay to do that?
Yes. Blocking the emergency door
is against the fire code.
If someone says something about it,
I'll just report them.
I see.
See you around.
Insurance companies always ask for 50, 50.
Maintaining a safe distance,
duty to look ahead, and such. Right?
Ignore what all those parrots say.
I saw the footage
and 90 to 10 is totally possible.
I'm from Unit 501.
I moved in today. Here's a greeting gift.
Just a minute, sir.
Since we're neighbors,
consultations will be free.
Please come by any time.
Okay.
Yes, I think that's fine.
(Lawyer Kook Hae-seong will appear
with a bang in difficult moments)
"Lawyer Kook Hae-seong
will appear with a bang"
"in difficult moments."
(Lawyer Kook Hae-seong will appear
with a bang in difficult moments)
That's separate. Yes.
(Quit Chat)
(What do I have to do to become a lawyer?)
Yes, call me again after you check it.
(Park Chan-hyeok)
I think that's a separate matter.
(It's a hit-and-run. I didn't do it, my friend did.)
(It was late at night.)
Yes.
(There weren't any cameras.)
(They think they hit someone.)
Of course. Call me any time.
(How can I know if it's been reported?)
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
(Is your friend going to turn themself in?)
-Who was it?
-Downstairs neighbor.
She moved in.
And? You're throwing food away?
How can someone, who was my secretary
and now my wife, trust people so easily?
You shouldn't eat what strangers give you.
So you're saying
the woman living downstairs
gave us poisoned food to kill us.
Honey, you have an illness.
So-yoon, I was a public defender.
I became aware of the malice
in humans really early.
Right. As a public defender,
go and give the client consultation.
I think he needs a lawyer.
Come on.
(Will my friend get caught if they don't?)
Of course, they will, you punk.
The police are probably
on their way to your house right now.
What is it?
(I'll have to see if the accident
has been reported first.)
(Can I get in touch with your friend?
And as quickly as possible.)
Who are you?
Hello.
I moved in downstairs.
I came to give you some rice cakes.
I don't like flour.
Rice cakes are made of rice.
It was nice to meet you too!
Honey.
Honey!
Yes?
Welcome back.
The doorbell rang,
so why didn't you open the door?
I was washing my hair.
But is the door lock broken?
Why'd you ring the doorbell?
I didn't ring it.
The person living downstairs came.
Seriously.
Not only is the house tiny,
but the security is also a mess.
Min-ji, wash your hands first.
If you come home, you have to
wash your hands for 20 seconds.
You're taking your medicine? Hold on.
Here's your water.
Here.
I got five complaints today.
They're only getting a few fillers,
so why are they asking for so much?
This is the very reason I didn't want
to open a dermatology franchise.
I'm sorry.
You took on something annoying
because of me.
I'll whip up your favorite
ice-cold tangerine highball.
My gosh, your legs are so stiff.
I'll loosen it up for you today.
Stop it.
But first, a cup of tangerine highball?
Ma'am.
Why are you being so kind today?
(Reusable Garbage Disposal Bag)
Let's see.
(Collect the coupons!)
Let's collect 20 coupons
and get a small tangsuyuk for free.
Sure.
Right.
This.
What is it?
A contract stating
we'll jointly own the house
once it switches
to general sales after ten years.
It's 60 to 40, but it's fine right?
I did earn more points.
Of course. You even saved my life.
-Right?
-Yes.
I wanted the floor
to have a herringbone design.
But ripping the new floor apart
doesn't sit right.
This is neat too.
I can't believe it.
My house!
As for the curtains,
something natural like white
or beige sounds nice, doesn't it?
-Yes.
-Should we put up blinds on the balcony?
I think the lighting is perfect.
But how about we buy
some lights for decoration?
Let's buy some exercise equipment
for this room.
Good idea.
I prefer stainless steel
for the countertop.
But this is completely new too.
Let's use this for now
and change it later.
How about we change the faucet
of the sink and the bathroom?
Sure.
I've got to earn lots.
But still, it's nice, isn't it?
It'll be worth earning money.
You're right. I'll earn lots too.
We can do it!
I heard someone
from the district office might visit.
Should I move it?
No, good job.
We need to be careful until the very end.
You're right.
My family had a house when I was young.
I don't know what went wrong,
but we kept moving into smaller houses,
and in the end,
we moved into a semi-basement house.
It only had one room.
Back in high school?
Yes.
During the day,
I could roam around outside,
but I still have to sleep at night.
So I'd go home as late as I could
and when I did,
my family
would sleep side-by-side
in that tiny room.
Mom and dad fought every single day.
When I couldn't put up with it any longer,
I'd leave the house with my dad's car key.
(I can't believe it!)
(You only get paid peanuts,)
(so how do you expect us to live on now?)
(Can't you see how hard
I'm trying to save up money?)
(Facility construction)
I wanted my own space.
My very own space.
I almost have it now.
The world had better not collapse now.
Good night.
You will end up like this too.
What's wrong?
What are they doing
in the middle of the night?
Do you want me to go upstairs?
No, it's okay.
I was just startled. That's all.
Hello?
(No Notifications)
Right now?
-Who was that?
-What?
Just a guy I know. He called
because of a case we're investigating.
Go back to sleep. You're on holiday.
Why must you draw Sae-bom's blood?
She's already exhausted.
We don't take much.
I'm the one who got you married,
so don't be rude to me.
(We welcome all new residents.)
What does that have to do with you?
I made it happen on my own.
Had I not gotten her the extra points,
she would've never asked you to marry her.
Anyway, you managed to sneak
into our building.
Did you see the news
about the homeless shelter?
-I did.
-Later in the day,
a report will be released
that people there were given Next.
In case there are any side effects,
the product will be completely
taken off the market,
and anyone who's caught selling them
will be punished severely.
That is the government's plan.
And why are you telling me all this?
Because we have to
work on this together.
We've sent an official request
for a joint investigation.
I'm a busy man.
As you see, I'm...
(Captain)
Hello, sir.
Yes.
Do I have to do it?
Sure, okay.
Who else would do it, if not me?
Got it.
So?
What should I do first?
It's Lee Jong-tae's phone.
We've unlocked it.
We need you to meet and arrest the dealer
pretending to be him.
So Lee Jong-tae is working with us too?
Something like that.
Do you know
why drug-related cases are so tough?
These jerks never trust anyone,
and they're awfully greedy on top of that.
They won't agree to meet
unless we pay at least half up front.
But the police don't have the money
to do that.
It's not that I don't want to help.
The investigation won't go anywhere...
Use this for the investigation.
Bring back receipts if possible,
and return the rest.
I heard you used to work
at a pharmaceutical company.
In a team called "Competitive" something.
Competitive Advantage.
It's a department that steals
rival companies' products.
I couldn't make anything,
but I had a knack for stealing.
And for beating people up.
Call me when you have the dealer.
I should be there as an observer.
How much is this, exactly?
You'd better not lie
about the amount later on.
Senior Officer Jung Yi-hyun.
Your nickname is Sherlock
because you always use logic
to solve cases.
My colleagues say I'm reckless and lazy,
but also lucky.
I get bizarre ideas,
but they always work,
for some strange reason.
People assume that athletes are dumb.
Why don't you take this
as an opportunity to prove
that you are smart and athletic?
I really can't stand that guy.
(Scrapbook)
(Ms. Kim Bok-nam)
Hi, Mom. What's up?
(I heard you moved
into the apartment yesterday.)
I can't believe you didn't even call me.
My goodness.
Must I hear about you through Yi-hyun?
I'm exhausted now, Mom.
I was tested for an infectious disease.
(I got the Covid-19 test
more than five times.)
No, not that.
You know, the biting disease
that everyone's talking about these days.
The mad person disease?
It has a name?
Yes, the name came from "mad dog disease,"
also known as rabies.
They say people can get rabies too.
(My goodness.)
(That's why dog owners are
so stressed out these days.)
Yes. That thing.
I'm in quarantine now, after being tested
for the "mad person disease."
I bit someone in my dream last night.
Really?
What does Yi-hyun say?
Is he okay being around you?
Yes, of course.
We love each other so much, you know.
I'll get well soon and call you
as soon as we have the date
for our wedding.
I can't stop coughing. I have to go.
We need groceries.
(Gym Membership)
(Hours of Operation)
(Weekdays: 6 a.m. to 10 p.m.
Weekends: 6 a.m. to 9 p.m.)
-Hi.
-Hello.
What is that? A duel request?
Let me see that.
(Thank you for the rice cakes)
Oh my gosh.
How pretty.
(Thank you for the rice cakes)
Thanks.
They deliver, you know.
Yes, I saw.
Ask your family to order from them
if you want rice cakes later.
Anyway, are you really a cop?
Yes, of course.
See?
It's better than a cop.
I want to become like you
if I become healthy.
Are you sick?
A little.
I was really sick a long time ago
and missed school for two years.
-Really?
-Yes.
But I'm healthy now.
You'll become stronger than I am,
so don't worry at all. I mean it.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
To duel.
May I help you?
I live downstairs.
You were loud all night long.
Are you renovating?
I'm sorry.
I was moving some furniture around.
In the middle of the night?
I tend to spring to action
once I get an idea.
I always have to do it right away.
Sorry about that.
That's an illness, actually.
It won't happen again.
I'd appreciate it.
Thanks for the rice cake.
How did you know it was from me?
-I don't think we've met.
-I heard.
She's pretty. She takes after you.
You're pretty.
Haven't you seen him before?
I've seen him a few times in the elevator,
but he doesn't seem to care
about other people.
Both he and his wife are doctors
but he bums around at home.
My mom says he has a legal problem.
I see. Or he may just like bumming around.
-Bye.
-What about you?
Me? I want to work out.
Have a nice day.
Are you home alone?
My dad makes deliveries.
My mom helps him sort
through the items in the morning.
What about school?
I'm doing online learning at home.
If you tell them in advance,
you can skip 19 days of school every year.
I see.
Come with me.
Today, you'll have gym class.
Physical education.
(Indoor driving range)
So here it is.
(New Residents Special)
(Safe Clean Zone)
Hello.
This is nice.
-Hello.
I'm a resident. I was told
that I could use it whenever I want.
Just a minute.
You have to bring your own sneakers,
towels, and the like.
Please fill out your information here.
(Visitors' Log)
Hi there.
Hello.
Are you going to exercise too?
Yes.
-Here.
-Okay. Thank you.
(Yoon Sae-bom, Building 101, Unit 501)
So...
Public housing residents
don't have access.
Why not? Because of maintenance fees?
Yes, that too, but...
Because of the price of the equipment.
Some people say it's unfair
to let public housing residents use them
when the residents of the regular units
are the ones who paid for them.
I see. Fine. I'll work out at home then.
-Let's go.
-Wait. Excuse me.
But if you get personal training from me,
I can waive that requirement for you.
I'll work out at home.
Did you know?
Yes.
(We welcome all new residents.)
Then why didn't you tell me?
Because I thought you could fix it.
Isn't there another fire code
or something?
It's difficult when money's involved.
(Le Ciel)
There is a way though.
-One.
-Two.
-Three.
Slowly. Four.
Four.
Good. Five.
Five.
Let's move on.
What do they do at school
during gym class?
-Running.
-Do you run well?
No.
I'm really good.
(Wife)
(Missed Call: Wife)
Get lots of rest since you exercised.
Bye.
She's so cute.
-Hey.
(-Sae-bom.)
(Help me.)
(I was)
scratched by that trainee that day.
I was too scared to tell you,
but the wound won't heal.
Where are you?
I'll come to you.
It's okay.
Look at me. I'm fine.
Get tested today
and rest up. You'll be fine.
I'll tell your wife
you're not having an affair.
The thought of dying scares me.
Why would you die?
You weren't bit.
Look at me.
It's nothing.
Get tested today and confirm
that you're fine. Then it'll all be good.
I'll ask them to give you extra points.
You're not thirsty or anything, right?
(Stop)
I'm bringing in a patient.
Let me look at the wound.
Are you sure this is a scratch?
It looks like a knife wound.
It looks fresh too.
I wish it were as well.
You know my wound won't heal either.
It doesn't look too serious.
But let's run a test.
There we go.
What will be different
if there's a problem?
The color.
The wound will turn dark red.
Wait here until the results are out.
Aren't you going to uncuff me?
This should be enough for you to move.
Tell me if you get thirsty.
Ms. Yoon, step out for a minute.
I told you, didn't I?
You'll be fine.
I'll be back after I get my blood drawn.
It's okay.
Nothing will happen.
I'm just making money.
It's okay.
Tell me in advance
if something like this happens again.
I don't want to be surprised.
I will,
so can you open my bag?
I'm killing you with kindness.
Our trainee,
the one who was bitten by Lee Jong-tae.
I heard he's in bad condition
and that his family visit was rejected.
If you get bitten,
you'll get infected no matter what.
Your condition gets worse
and your time
as a normal person decreases.
You never know
when you'll get thirsty and attack others.
So it's only natural
that visits are restricted.
Is there a way to treat it?
None at the moment.
If it gets worse,
you'll always feel thirsty.
You lose reason and attack anyone you see.
The only thing we can do right now
is to slow down that process.
So it's true nobody made it out alive.
Ms. Yoon,
you're very lucky.
If everything is all right,
it'll be the same for Mr. Lee.
You're bored, right?
How about we grab some food?
Where are you right now?
I have a family.
I'll die in vain
and they'll keep it a secret.
(Sae-bom.)
There's a way I can ensure safety
and make money.
Hello? Hey, Lee Seung-young!
(The person you have reached
is not available.)
(Will they be okay?)
What if they all die in there?
I got a call from a reporter.
He said he'd pay me if I told him
(what happened here.)
He slipped out wearing
a quarantine uniform.
They thought he was hauling chairs.
Where are the critically ill patients?
Where are they?
They were isolated in an underground
low-temperature food ingredient warehouse.
But the number kept increasing.
We had no choice but to move them.
To where?
The refrigerator truck.
Darn it.
(One big bill for an exclusive video
and other incentives for high ratings.)
(Trash Journalist)
Wire me the money first.
Then I'll send the video right away.
This conversation is being recorded,
so don't think you can dupe me later.
Then send me at least half!
Call me after you send me the money.
This is
a huge scoop.
(Seyang Dream Car Wash)
Why not go in if he's in there?
I'm waiting for someone.
Who? Did you call for backup?
Speak of the devil.
What? My goodness.
Lieutenant Colonel Han Tae-seok.
What brings you here?
The dealer.
Senior Officer Jung
and I will go meet him. Do you mind?
No, not at all. I'll just wait here.
-Hey--
-I know.
Stand guard.
I really can't stand him.
Why are you really here?
Next's manufacturer had the rest
of the supply stored in their warehouse.
I want to find out who released it.
I saw the news. It looks like this disease
has spread to other countries.
Was Next sold worldwide?
I told you I had a knack for stealing
although I was never good
at making things.
I stole it for a foreign company.
Back in my Competitive Advantage days.
He's really something.
There are three of them.
Hey, turn off the lights!
(Exit)
Did you bring the rest?
Where is Lee Jong-tae?
Well...
Jong-tae, that punk.
I can't reach him.
I only see these two.
There are three.
(Slow Down, Slippery)
The pills.
In the trunk.
Go ahead and cuff them.
You jerks are dead meat now.
What's that?
A Glock. First time seeing one?
Why do you even have that on you?
(Exit)
What are you doing?
Just making sure he's dead.
How could you kill a person
in front of a cop?
Does this look like a human to you?
Hands up!
Hands up.
It's over.
Really? My goodness.
Hey! How many shots did you fire?
Thank goodness they were blanks.
You could be reprimanded for this.
Did you do this?
Stop!
Please.
Wait! Stop!
When did he turn into that?
I don't know!
When I went to his place to get paid,
he was already like that.
He had bitten his family to death.
He was banging his head
on the bloody floor.
Did he take Next?
Yes, lots of it.
He totally lost his mind
and ended up like that.
And you used him like that?
What else is he good for?
He's the best guard dog
that doesn't need to be fed.
You guys took the pills too, didn't you?
You'll end up like him soon.
-Get up, jerk.
-Yes.
Okay.
Mr. Jung.
There's a problem at the dormitory.
What about it?
Ms. Yoon is there now.
What is she doing there?
(They're not human.)
What's not human?
(All of them.)
Quiet!
Open this truck.
Hurry!
No, don't open it!
=Happiness=
(Be honest.)
You think they're monsters.
They want the case dropped.
(The mad person disease is spreading
in the apartment complex.)
(That pill causes
the mad person disease, doesn't it?)
Bad rumors will only bring down
our property prices.
(Block all of them in as planned.)
(Lock them up
and just wait for them to die?)
There was definitely something off
about the lady upstairs.
(What is happening)
(inside the apartment?)