(Han Hyo-joo)
(Park Hyung-sik)
(Jo Woo-jin)
(Lee Jun-hyeok, Park Joo-hee)
(Bek Hyun-jin, Moon Ye-won)
(Park Hyoung-soo, Jeong Woon-seon)
(Bae Hae-sun, Cha Soon-bae)
(Park Hee-von, Na Chul, Han Jun-woo)
(Kim Young-woong, Lee Ji-ha,
Lee Ju-seung, Song Ji-u)
(Hong Soon-chang, Lee Ju-sil,
Kang Han-saem)
=Happiness=
(This program includes
indirect advertisements.)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(All characters, places, corporations,
and events are fictional.)
(Six months ago)
I saw a sign for half-priced baby goods.
I bought what I thought would suit
our Wriggly perfectly.
We don't know
if it'll be a boy or a girl.
It'll be a girl that looks like you.
That's what I say every day
as I pat my tummy.
No girl should ever look like me.
The chairman's here.
I'm nearly there.
- See you soon.
- Okay, bye.
Yes?
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
Thanks.
So, the Ministry of Food and Drug Safety
made the decision?
Yes. It'll be announced before noon tomorrow.
Under the condition, it's prescribed only
to adult ADHD patients.
Once it's proved to be effective,
they will expand the age group.
Good job.
All the Next pills we have in storage.
I was wondering if I should take them all.
Thanks to you, I'm about to become richer.
It's a failed pneumonia cure,
but I believe it'll help treat adult ADHD.
Yes. Word is already getting around...
that it helps you focus.
Lots of people I know are taking it.
- Is that Next?
- Yes.
- Have you taken it?
- No.
You should when you don't feel too well.
It makes you feel alive.
It's great.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Park Young In.
I heard a lot about you. Please, sit.
- Thank you.
- Sit.
- Is this it?
- Brace yourself for it.
So, are you expecting a prince or a princess?
Our Wriggly? I think it's a girl.
Oh, that's great.
They say that a daughter
is worth ten sons these days.
So they say.
- Excuse me for a moment.
- Sure.
When will we get to meet your princess?
I'm 12 weeks along,
so I guess in about six months?
Lovely.
He bites?
Is he taking something else?
They'll announce their approval tomorrow.
Have him admitted and silence the staff.
Word cannot get out.
He's not dead, so who cares?
Offer compensation and full treatment, then.
I'll call you back.
Honey.
Sir.
The Prime Minister called.
Where are they headed?
To a landfill.
There's not enough room to house mild cases.
Do you still not get...
what I'm doing?
I do, sir.
I made a choice.
On how many losses we can stand to take.
The time will come...
when you must decide
how much blood you should shed.
How about the cure?
We selected a few options...
and administered them to the infected.
They all died.
Try again. Do it until it works.
I'll buy us time.
=Happiness=
=Episode 6=
Then what do we do?
There are infected people outside.
But we won't be getting any help
from the authorities.
We have to force our way
out of this apartment complex.
They even installed barricades at every wall.
Even if we force our way out of here,
where are we going to go next?
We can get out of here first...
and get into the most expensive apartment complex.
What are they going to do then?
Will they seal off that apartment too?
All the rich people probably all live there.
They can do whatever they want with us...
because our apartment isn't that expensive.
Goodness.
Are you sure there are infected people outside?
The resident representative
and Mr. Oh aren't here.
This is about the public rental units again?
All I'm pointing out is that the people
who went outside...
didn't attend this meeting. That's all.
If you want to leave, go ahead.
I can't guarantee
that you will be able to come back.
Then I'll assume
that we're all on the same page.
We brought some stuff and food from the supermarket.
We left them in Unit 201.
So if you need anything, go there.
But they will probably need more stuff.
So you can exchange what you have
with what they have.
Hey, what if the infected people
break into the building...
when their symptoms get worse?
If they crash the door with a car,
the door will break.
They will probably look
for an easier way to break in.
That's how crimes all begin.
"I went in because the door was open."
"There was no lock on the bicycle.
So I took it."
Breaking the door
because they are thirsty for blood...
Getting that kind of determination isn't common.
So we don't have to give them
a reason to break in.
We already locked all the doors.
What is it?
The rooftop.
I'm the only one here.
Do you think they heard us?
Let's hope not.
You never get startled, Andrew.
You were calm outside and here too.
I'm happy
that people don't treat me like a weirdo.
You two should be careful.
You too, Andrew.
Let's get some fresh air before we head back down.
Gosh. I'm exhausted.
Seriously.
Standing here reminds me of that day.
When?
You mean, that day?
Hey.
Gosh. I really wondered
if I could fly for a split second.
You did fly.
I did.
If I could fly, I would go visit my mom
in the nursing home.
I felt uncomfortable to see her,
so I kept pushing it off.
And look what happened now.
What do you think happened
to those infected people?
Are they hiding somewhere...
and enduring their thirst?
They must be scared...
that they might bite someone closest to them...
and become a complete monster.
But they'll keep fighting
until they cave into their thirst.
Everyone is okay. Right?
Of course.
We have to make sure we don't get hurt.
That way, we can see them again.
Exactly. Don't you ever do something
like that again.
Hey.
Why did you touch that blood?
For all I know, it could've been dangerous.
So you're fine with me rubbing it
on Oh Ju Hyung's face?
You didn't make him lick it.
I doubt that he'd lick that blood.
Never.
Gosh. It looked like
he really cared a lot about his health.
Seeing how he didn't come to the meeting,
he must feel somewhat intimidated.
And the resident representative
didn't come down either.
Are you all right?
Of course, not.
Look at this.
I must have been really stressed.
Darn it.
Given what happened, perhaps,
it's best to give up.
Looking at the current situation,
it'll be difficult to make money...
even if you become the representative.
And if we leave?
If we leave, we won't get a penny
for this apartment.
So your plan is to leave this apartment
after losing money...
and start over at a different apartment?
Well, we don't have many options.
You said that Seung Beom might have been infected too.
You went to the gym every day.
What did you do there?
You should've kept an eye on him.
Who knew he would do drugs?
Once the lockdown is over,
we'll have to repair the entire apartment complex.
We should replace the elevator interior...
and clean the outer walls too.
The lockdown was easier because of the walls.
Let's suggest planting trees around the complex.
You said you knew a landscaper. Right?
And we can even get the entire complex
to be disinfected...
since there are infected people.
Yes. That's it.
If we just change the way we think,
we have so many ways to make money off this.
By the way, do you think you can be...
the apartment representative?
I should win over some residents
that seem to have sway over people.
My father had schizophrenia.
He passed away two years ago.
So I easily get shocked
when I see people with similar disorders.
Sae Bom isn't home.
Darn it.
Okay.
You're the girl from Unit 502.
Then are you alone at home?
Where are the adults?
Can you open the door?
The adults are here.
You startled me.
I apologize...
for my action this afternoon.
By the way,
you should have clearly told me
that you were not infected.
Anyone would get the wrong idea
when they see blood.
Don't you agree?
It must be tough for you too.
But you are lucky that people are here
to look after you. Right?
I'm so lucky.
I'm so glad that we live on the lower floor.
You must be disappointed...
that you cannot enjoy your honeymoon phase...
because of the disease.
My husband and I started...
from the first floor of a small apartment.
And there was a flood
when we were living on the first floor.
Gosh. Those were such hard days.
How did you two meet?
Gosh.
You guys have a long history.
You can take a seat there.
I can't trust that lady.
Same here.
Then why did you invite her in?
Keep your friends close.
But keep your enemies closer.
Hey, what about Sae Bom?
She's talking to Ms. Oh.
She said she came to apologize.
Apologize?
I bet even her apology is annoying.
Yes.
It's because she's not sorry.
By the way,
she asked me
if I wanted to be the apartment representative.
She's eyeing that position then.
That's such a hassle. Why?
She made it sound like it came with a lot of money.
Hey, they make all the decisions
about hiring security guards...
and outsourcing all the services
during the representative meetings.
Elevators, outer wall, roof, garage,
electricity, and landscaping.
All of it. That's all money.
All of it?
Do you have any more?
I'm an athlete you know.
Can you give me another gimbap?
- Gimbap?
- Yes.
Wait.
Are you going to put handcuffs on me again?
I'm losing the circulation in my wrists.
- Kim Seung Beom.
- Yes?
The residents here are on high alert right now.
Up until now, nobody was able to tell,
so they let it go.
But soon enough,
they'll become suspicious of you.
So?
I'm telling you to be careful...
so that people don't get scared.
I can't do anything about the handcuffs tonight.
But if you're okay for the next few days,
I'll let you roam around in the gym freely.
You're not threatening me today.
I truly hope that you don't have this disease.
Because you're not the only problem...
in this apartment complex.
My gosh!
Darn it!
I'm going to kill them.
Just wait and see.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I'm fine.
See? Look. Isn't it clean?
Are you sure you're not scared?
You nearly scraped off your skin
washing your face.
Hey!
What are you eating?
(Hangover Medicine)
I thought you were eating something weird
that's bad for you.
Pour me a drink.
Have you...
ever seen Min Ji take medicine at the hospital?
Like vitamins or supplements.
She took something whenever she was tired.
What kind of medicine?
I don't know. It was a pill.
She said it was a supplement
she got from the gym.
The gym?
Your name wasn't on the access list to the gym.
My wife was the one who went to the gym.
Did the mad person disease
spread from the gym?
Why? Is it important?
Don't drink too much.
You don't want to get sick.
Where are you going?
Somewhere. Don't worry about it.
(Authorized Personnel Only)
(No food allowed, Fitness)
(Community Center)
- Go home first.
- Why?
I left my wallet.
Why did you bring your wallet?
I'll be right back.
Go wait at home.
(Community Center)
Who are you?
Someone really was here.
Hey. Mister.
Are you stuck here?
Yes, well... I guess I am.
The officer on the fifth floor
locked me in here.
Hey, mister.
Can you help me?
I really don't have any problems.
I'm really clean,
but the officer upstairs...
- The officer...
- Did you sell drugs...
to my wife?
The doctor on the sixth floor,
the one who died from mad person disease.
I'm not here to blackmail you.
Nor am I here to get revenge.
I'm grateful to you.
Hey, mister.
I want to buy some of that drug.
I really don't know anything about it.
- You don't?
- I really don't.
- You don't know?
- I don't.
- You don't?
My gosh.
You're really annoying me.
Should I kick you out of this place
saying you're sick? You lunatic!
My gosh.
Hold on.
- Hold on.
- You don't know anything.
Why are you doing this?
You don't know anything?
I really don't.
Mister. Hold on.
I don't know anything. Okay?
- Hey, mister.
- What don't you know?
Please.
- Stop. Please stop!
- Get over here.
Yes, are you Attorney Kook Hae Seong?
Yes, I am.
I live in Building 102,
and I'm here
because I saw your ad on the elevator.
I heard there are a lot of patients outside.
It's not true. There were a few,
but we locked them up in the children's library.
Building 101 is being sensitive and limiting entrance.
So are you saying it's not that serious right now?
Right. Can we meet for a second...
and talk?
It's about my grandfather's grave site.
Where are you right now?
Basement Level 1.
Can we meet and talk?
The Internet works down here.
It'll be easier for me
to show you a map too.
Stay right there.
I'll be right down.
Weren't you talking to someone?
I don't know.
It sounded like someone outside.
I'm going to step out for a second.
Where are you going?
I'm feeling stuffy in here.
I'm going to cool off
by taking a walk.
(Working from home)
(Search Visitors)
(We are looking it up.
Please wait a moment.)
Yes, are you Attorney Kook Hae Seong?
What's wrong?
- Hello.
- Hi.
My husband went out to meet someone
from another building.
I remember hearing...
there were a lot of
mad person disease patients outside.
Excuse me.
Where is he?
No! Help me!
I was hoping he didn't have it.
Hey! Help me!
- Do something about this lunatic!
- Why should I?
The world would be a better place
without you in it.
Hey! Help me!
Hello, sir.
We're all stuck inside,
so I couldn't go out to get a consultation.
Okay. Hold on.
(You're not connected to a network.)
The Internet isn't working.
You have to come out over here.
Over here.
How do I unlock the door?
You're lucky.
If it weren't for Sae Bom,
you'd be dead.
Do you see that camera?
If you tell anyone about this guy,
I'll send everyone a video of him grabbing you.
People will think you're infected.
Do you get what I'm saying?
So...
stay at home and just breathe.
Why...
Why are you hiding the fact...
that he's sick?
Because he's a person.
Mr. Kim.
Calm down.
You can become normal again.
Mister.
The complex is under lockdown.
Go home...
and get some sleep.
Lady.
What was that about? You startled me.
Stay still.
We don't want him to break in.
Mister.
I told you earlier
that you shouldn't go outside.
He was a client!
He wanted to discuss his grandfather's land.
Didn't you see he was just fine?
I just saved you from getting buried.
You just lost me a client.
What are you on about?
Are you jinxing me?
Honey.
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
- Did you tell her?
- What?
Why did you do that?
Darn it.
You just won't stand down, will you?
I should toss you to him
and get you infected.
- Guess what?
- What?
I am...
incredibly...
lucky, you see.
Take this.
That's disgusting.
There is...
someone outside, okay?
There you are.
Your husband's out of his mind!
Did you touch him?
What is wrong with you people?
Your husband...
hit my face while I was wearing my glasses.
Attempted murder...
No. He tried to kill me.
Come here.
He tried to...
get that monster to kill me.
What's that?
- What is that?
- Are you okay?
Kim Seung Beom's infected.
Hey.
It's dangerous. Stay back.
I will kill you.
I will kill you all.
Did you know we had a patient inside?
Then you should've told us!
The trainer in the basement gym.
I think he's sick.
There's someone down there?
How is he?
Hey...
At around 10:45 or 10:46pm,
he stopped banging his head.
You go upstairs.
I'll check things out.
Be careful.
You're awake, aren't you?
You're awake.
The people upstairs...
will be talking about throwing you out.
Darn it.
I only took the pill twice.
They said it was a good pick-me-up
when you're tired.
Why did you go to your car?
To get the rest of my pills.
I can focus better on them.
You thought of taking a pill
in that situation?
I really only took it twice.
Do you remember what happened
when you turned?
A bit.
The guy from the sixth floor came in
and said something.
I tried to hold back,
but he kept talking.
It would be best
if you hold back from now on.
The more often you turn,
the harder it becomes to come back.
I told that guy about the pills.
That they're in the gym's van.
I'll deal with that.
Was it fun?
Do you enjoy yourself
when you have a fit?
Is it exciting and thrilling?
Is it?
Then you can't hold back for long.
It's cold at night.
Wear something warm.
How's the gym guy?
He's back to normal now.
He turns for about 15 minutes,
then switches back.
We'll vote tomorrow.
- On what?
- Kim Seung Beom.
Whether he should stay or go.
The sixth-floor lawyer said...
we were a democracy,
so we should vote to decide
To be honest, I thought I was nasty.
But here, I have nothing on the other guys.
Didn't the resident representative complain?
All she cares about
is being the apartment representative.
If we side with her,
she'll cancel our management fees.
Jung Guk was right, then.
About...
what Oh Ju Hyung said.
It's a lie, isn't it?
What is?
That I tried to kill him?
That's not true. He...
He was threatening the gym guy,
- so I threatened him back.
- Right?
Yes.
It got to me a bit.
You know how I can't keep things to myself
and stew on them.
I know that.
Sae Bom.
- The good cop, bad cop strategy.
- What's that?
When one plays the bad cop
and gets angry and scares people,
the other uses nice words to persuade them.
Carrot and stick.
- What about it?
- I'll play the bad cop.
You play the good cop.
- No.
- What?
You already played the bad cop an awful lot.
I'll be the bad cop.
I'll beat up anyone I find annoying.
So you have to be nice. Okay?
Be nice.
Hey.
I don't want you to get hurt...
because that's what happens...
to bad cops.
We must release him.
Only then we can survive.
Is he the only one?
Is everyone else okay?
Did anyone get bitten?
We don't know that yet.
But we must release him
once his symptoms show.
Sir.
Can you share this video with me?
You'll agree to releasing him. Right?
Of course. I already saw a bunch
of infected people outside.
- Gosh.
- Hey. I was watching that.
- Why did you take it from me?
- Please vote with me.
Things are getting serious.
You agree, don't you?
This is it.
I was so scared after seeing that.
You understand
why I behaved that way, right?
Is that what's important now?
Hey, look at his eyes.
Where's Mr. Oh Ju Hyung?
He's constantly washing himself.
If you want,
I can let you take an empty room
in my house.
You can stay with us too.
I appreciate you looking out for me.
Do you have to make house calls?
Of course.
Imagine I opened the door earlier.
That guy from the next building
would have killed me off instantly.
He talked about the grave site
and tried to kill me.
What if we get infected too?
Why would we?
We didn't do anything wrong.
You don't get sick
because you do something wrong.
Anyway, I'm not leaving my house
until the lockdown is lifted.
It will only take five minutes.
You can save a man with those five minutes.
Are you sure they are even human?
I'm talking about the infected people.
Of course. You can talk to him
if you go down to the gym.
A man might die because...
you won't leave your house.
Please think about this.
Please think about it.
What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
Where did you go?
To the 15th floor. I asked him to come down
for the vote tomorrow.
Have you ever regretted something in your life?
Well...
I have.
When something happens,
but it ends before I get to give it my all,
it leaves me a lot of regrets.
I still remember stuff like that
even after years pass by.
That makes me feel guilty.
So you don't want any regrets this time?
Right.
This time I'll face it head-on.
(Monthly gym membership, 30 dollars)
Bingo.
What?
Let's go.
Okay.
Mom, let me borrow your phone.
Why?
I'll give it back after I take a video.
I lost mine.
Where did you lose your phone?
I thought you had a new phone.
Mom, you don't use it
except for making calls. Right?
What's the passcode?
It's not locked.
Thank you.
Return it right back
once you're done taking photos.
Okay, I will. Goodness.
- Let's go.
- Go.
Thank you all for coming
during your busy days.
Article 22 of our Penal Code states...
a regulation regarding emergency evacuations.
Let me read that for you.
"An act performed to avoid..."
"impending danger against one's own
or other person's legal interest..."
"shall not be punishable
when there are reasonable grounds."
"The provisions of the preceding paragraph
shall not apply..."
"to a person who cannot avoid the danger."
Let me put it in layman's terms.
The law allows us...
to kick him out for the safety of the group.
I doubt that you guys want...
to get infected like the other buildings.
Correct?
Let me play this for you.
It's very scary. Take a look.
Oh, Lord.
Who here has had COVID-19?
Why are you bringing up COVID-19 now?
No one?
I did catch it once. Why?
Let me ask you something.
Sir, did you catch COVID-19
because you did something wrong?
That's ridiculous!
I didn't do anything wrong.
I wouldn't have gotten it
if my friends invited me out...
for a meal.
Right. Diseases...
don't pick who gets them or not.
Right.
Do you remember how it was
during the COVID-19 outbreak?
Some people dug up...
personal information of infected people and criticized them.
But other people were worried
about the infected people...
and wished them to recover.
The infected people shouldn't be kicked out
without a chance...
to get treated.
This is not COVID-19.
It's different.
They are violent and try to bite other people.
I understand that you are all scared and anxious.
I feel the same way.
But what if this happened to you...
or your family?
Who will we kick out next
after Trainer Kim Seung Beom?
Mr. Oh Ju Hyung from the sixth floor?
Or you since you had contact with Mr. Oh?
Should we play musical chairs...
until there's only one of us left?
Whatever. Let's vote.
Raise your hands if you vote for releasing him.
Look. We don't have to release him.
I just want to isolate him
from other healthy people.
We can put him on the rooftop
and isolate him completely.
That way, it will be safe for all of us.
- Don't you agree?
- Well...
Don't be timid. Just voice your opinions.
Why won't you speak up?
Hurry. Raise your hands.
Raise your hands now.
Come on.
Go ahead.
Ms. Oh! How could you do this to me?
How? You made me come here!
I was nice to him.
So I guess he feels betrayed.
So eight people voted for it.
So Yoon, what are you doing?
Raise your hand now.
Hey.
Nine.
Then who is against it?
One, two,
three,
four,
five,
six...
Six,
seven,
eight,
nine.
We're tied. What should we do now?
Should we take another vote?
I don't think we need to.
I vote...
that we don't kick him out.
Ten votes. We're done.
That's good.
I wasn't comfortable with the idea...
of kicking someone in our apartment out.
You know I don't have any personal feelings
towards you, right?
Okay, then.
Let's discuss how we'll keep an eye
on Mr. Kim from now on?
It's too hard for me, my husband,
and Detective Kim Jung Guk
to watch him on our own.
Let's break up into groups of two...
and take turns checking on him.
Who wants to start?
Should we be democratic...
and vote on it?
We'll go first.
Hurry up and open the barricades!
How frustrating.
Hurry up!
- What are you doing?
- Come on!
- Open it up!
- Open it!
- Let us through!
- Come on!
How long are you going to keep us here?
We have to get through!
- How long are you going to keep us?
- Let us go through!
I heard you told the prime minister's office...
that the areas with the most infection
must be controlled first.
I told them that
once the number of the infected goes up,
there's nothing we can do to stop it.
Makes sense.
You don't have a cure.
The best you can do is keep them cool...
and stall with some sedatives and sleeping pills.
You don't have much time left, right?
You have about a month.
The same goes for your wife.
Didn't she get infected
around the same time?
I thought
that was why you said you'd come up...
with a cure in a month.
I understand that you're in a hurry.
I'm going to give up...
on the current restricted areas.
You barely supported us until now.
Like you said,
we can't have any more infected people.
Cut the power...
and don't give them food.
The entire nation has their air conditioners on,
so we don't need to waste any more energy.
So you want to cut the power...
and wait for the infected to die on their own?
There will still be problems
even if there is a cure.
Anyone who has had a taste of blood...
can't be forgiven just because it happened
when they were sick.
You're the one...
who's addicted to the taste of blood.
It's okay for me to be.
I'm telling you
so that you know in advance.
Because you seem to have a plan.
Shouldn't we stop him?
If they cut the power,
the water will come next.
Then even those
who aren't infected will end up dying.
Find out when they're planning
on cutting the power.
Hey.
Why do you think I married you?
If you're my secretary, act like one...
and follow my lead without me explaining it.
We're married now.
You and I can have different opinions.
I still don't think that I was wrong.
So will you take responsibility
if we get infected?
This is why I shouldn't have married
someone so uneducated.
I think...
I made a mistake.
Dong Hyun.
- Give me my phone.
- Gosh.
Mom. I need to finish filming
to give it back to you.
Why are you nagging me so much today?
Do you have something on this phone?
What would I have on the phone?
Just wait a bit. Okay?
I'm going to go out to see
if there's anything more to film. Okay?
Dong Hyun. Hey.
Mom!
I'll give it back to you soon.
My gosh.
I need something impactful
for my views to go up.
What is this old lady doing?
My gosh.
Excuse me.
Did you lose your phone?
How did you know that?
You dropped it when we came in.
Right out front.
So...
How did you know I was looking for it?
You were filming something with it
on our way back yesterday.
You're filming right now as well.
I thought you might be looking for it.
Excuse me!
Ms. Lee?
Can you help me?
I'm not going to go outside.
I'll give you money.
Don't you need money?
Let me know if you need anything.
Can I ask you for a gun?
Do you think I'd give you one?
Why are you so interested in military goods?
I'm very interested in the apocalypse.
The Earth is in danger right now.
Even without a contagious disease, unusual weather,
global warming, nuclear war, artificial intelligence...
The end of the world is nearing.
I see.
That's why...
I'm in the process of collecting survival equipment.
I have combat rations from all over the world too.
Do you have a lot?
Of combat rations.
Do you want to...
take a look at my collection?
You have a collection?
May I?
Can't you break it
if you use a bit of strength?
I'm not sure.
If you break that,
your life will break apart too.
If you don't want to be kicked out,
you should be careful.
Are you here to tease me?
I'm here to clear up our misunderstanding.
I wanted to help you too.
But you're the one who took the drug.
When did you help me?
Drink it when you get thirsty.
Only when you can't bear it anymore.
I came because I was worried.
Why did you agree to come?
- Be quiet.
- What?
Tell me if you need anything.
Sometimes it seems like
you have a mental disorder.
Are you crazy?
How could you say that to your little sister?
I'm telling you that you do.
I can't believe you're really my brother.
Think about it.
I told you to be quiet.
I comforted him as the resident representative.
I thought
the young man would be having a hard time.
Excuse me.
I voted...
to kick him out earlier.
Do you think he remembers?
There are others he hates even more,
so you'll be fine.
The virus doesn't travel through the air,
so don't worry.
Keep an eye on him.
If he shows signs of extreme thirst,
do not give him any water
and come to the fifth floor. Okay?
- Okay.
This is the key to his handcuffs.
You won't need it,
but just in case.
I'll have a word with him.
Okay.
Hey. Aren't you scared?
Why would you vote yes
when you don't live here?
What did you tell Ms. Oh?
Forget about that.
I know something you want to know.
There's a lot I want to know right now.
The buyer.
The guy in the Hazmat suit.
The last voter.
- Exercise increases muscles.
- Yes.
If you take one of these,
you'll get double the result
compared to just working out.
If you look, it's a small pill.
The 15th floor.
It was right there.
I don't see it from here.
Hurry over there and get it.
I'll stand guard from here.
Let's move all this.
(Fire Trucks Only)
Hello.
Are you looking for something?
Shall I help you?
Sae Bom. Kim Seung Beom says...
Seo Yoon. Where's Sae Bom?
She went upstairs with the guy
from the 15th floor.
(We can chat if you're bored.)
Gosh. They're so cute.
Hyun Kyung. This is Jae Yeol.
He's such a good pianist.
When you write a novel about music,
he could help you out.
Then just lend me the money.
Aren't you worried about your wife and kids?
Talk about that when the lockdown's lifted.
I bet they're just fine.
Would they not be?
I'm working.
Let's be frank. If you die in here,
then your apartment becomes mine.
I followed you down here to help you out.
That sounds like you'll kill me.
You tried to once before.
You pushed me off a swing
and I ended up with this scar!
This is why I always have bangs!
Were you a great sister to me, then?
I had to retake the SAT
because you gave me hepatitis!
Blame that on your weak immune system!
Do you know how it feels
to have to bow to people your age?
Let's talk outside.
Darn it.
Hey. I'm sorry.
I'm not saying
I'm making plans to do something to you.
I think it's unfair, that's all.
What do you think is so unfair?
You went to university,
and when you got married,
you got an inheritance.
I only got tuition for one semester.
I worked and paid the rest.
But I didn't complain.
And now you're coming to me
as if you left me money?
I'm sorry about all that,
but let's not be too harsh.
We're still family.
Family, my foot.
What's that noise?
- We're safe here, aren't we?
- What?
What was that noise anyway?
(Community Center)
It's fine. We're safe here.
Don't... Get over here!
What are you doing?
Go! Run!
Run away!
I don't hear anyone.
Don't open the door.
Don't talk like that to me.
I'm your older brother.
Are you scared?
I'm right here. Don't be.
Darn it.
Did something happen outside?
Sae Bom.
She's in here, isn't she?
She's busy right now.
She'll be right out. Wait here.
Did you take the pill...
you bought at the gym?
If you hurt Sae Bom...
I will kill you.
=Happiness=
Someone's missing because of you.
We have the power.
We need people.
Someone who will do as we say.
Water doesn't help with the thirst.
It's Na Soo Min's phone.
They'll cut the power tonight.
Go.
You stay here.
I'm here for Sae Bom.
I'm here for even the smallest possibility.
If need be,
I'll get that person bitten.